mariasharapova.com 2012-06-21

# Privacy Policy - Maria Sharapova Official Website

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy _( **Policy** )_ sets forth the policies regarding the collection and use of information relating to the official Maria Sharapova web site located at www.mariasharapova.com ****( ** _Site_** ), which is operated by SW19, Inc. _(W **e**_ , or **_us_** _)_.  When we refer to SW19, Inc., we or us, we mean our entire company and all of its affiliated entities.

**Information We Collect and how we use it**

**_Personal Information_** means information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, email address, telephone number or similar information.  SW19, Inc. only collects Personal Information that you choose to share with us, such as when contacting us via the Site (e.g., by clicking on "Contact Us" or "Feedback" links or signing up for notifications or newsletters).

Use of Personal Information

We may use your Personal Information to send periodic marketing or promotional notices to you or notify you of any changes to this Policy.  We may also use your Personal Information to improve our marketing efforts, statistically evaluate site usage, improve the Site or customize the Site's content, layout and services. You can always opt-out of receiving these communications from us by following the "opt-out" procedures described below.

General

Any information you provide to SW19, Inc. must be true, accurate, current, non-misleading, and consistent and relevant for the purpose for which you are providing the information.

If you contact us via the Site, we will only use your Personal Information contained in your email to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the email.  We may retain your email for a period of time, but will not use any of your Personal Information for any purpose other than responding to your email.

Usage Data

The Site may automatically track certain information about your behavior while visiting the Site.  The information gathered includes only the URL from which you accessed this Site, and which URL you visit next.  We may collect and store this aggregate information in order to measure the Site's performance and improve the Site's design and functionality.  We may also share this aggregate information with third parties to illustrate how the Site is used and for other marketing purposes.

Cookies

The Site may use "cookies" or "session cookies," which is information stored in a browser's memory and passed back to the applicable server whenever a request for a new page on the Site is made.

**Use and Disclosure**

Subject to applicable law, we and our Service Providers (as described below) may disclose your Personal Information:

  * To Maria Sharapova and entities affiliated with SW19, Inc. and/or Maria Sharapova;
  * To unaffiliated third parties that are under contract to perform services for or on behalf of SW19, Inc. and/or Maria Sharapova ( ** _Service Providers_** ), and are required to uphold and maintain SW19, Inc. policies with respect to privacy and the treatment of your Personal Information (e.g., vendors maintaining our computer databases or performing marketing activities for SW19, Inc. and/or Maria Sharapova);
  * To other persons as permitted by applicable law or regulation; and
  * To law enforcement personnel and agencies, or as part of a legal process, in order to protect our property or in furtherance of an investigation regarding a breach of the Site rules and policies, unauthorized access to or use of the Site or any other illegal activities.

Any access to such information will be limited to the purpose for which such information was provided to our affiliate, subsidiary or Service Provider.  Our affiliates, subsidiaries and Service Providers may be located throughout the world.  Accordingly, information may be sent worldwide to countries which have a different level of privacy protection than the United States.

**Consent to Processing**

By using the Site, or providing information to SW19, Inc., you understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, processing, transfer and use of information in the United States and other countries and territories, for the purposes set forth in this Policy.  You hereby consent to the collection, processing and disclosure by SW19, Inc.  of your Personal Information as described under this Policy, including but not limited to the transfer of your Personal Information between SW19, Inc. 's Service Providers, affiliates and subsidiaries in accordance with this Policy.  For further certainty, any consent relating to a right to transfer information referred to in this paragraph shall be deemed to include your consent to the transfer of the applicable Personal Information to a jurisdiction which may have a different level of privacy protection than that available in your own country.

**Opt-Out Choices**

To "opt-out" of (1) receiving communications from SW19, Inc.  (except for communications necessary for your use of the Site), (2) having your Personal Information disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes, or (3) any other consent previously granted for a specific purpose concerning your Personal Information, send an e-mail to SW19, Inc.  at [feedback@mariasharapova.com](mailto:feedback@mariasharapova.com)

**Reviewing or Changing Information**

If you have provided Personal Information to us, you may request to review, change or delete your information previously provided to us by sending an e-mail to [feedback@mariasharapova.com](mailto:feedback@mariasharapova.com) Requests for changes to or deletions of your Personal Information should be made by you directly.

**Other Web Sites**

This Policy applies only to www.mariasharapova.com.  This Site includes links to other web sites, including access to content, products and services of such sites ( ** _Other Sites_** ).  In some cases, these Other Sites are made available via "framing technology", and may appear to be part of this Site. Although some of the entities controlling these linked or framed sites may be under contract with SW19, Inc., we urge you to familiarize yourself with the individual privacy and other terms for each linked or framed site prior to submitting your Personal Information.

**Sale or Transfer of Information**

In the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, dissolution, or sale or transfer of substantially all of the assets of SW19, Inc., Personal Information and/or Usage Data collected about you from the Site may be sold, assigned, or transferred to the party acquiring all or substantially all of the equity and/or assets of SW19, Inc.  in order to permit the party to continue the operation of the Site.  Subject to your ability to opt-out as described above, by using this Site and submitting your information to us, you consent to the sale and transfer of your information as described in this paragraph.

**Security**

SW19, Inc.  takes seriously the security of the information it collects. SW19, Inc.  has therefore implemented technology and security policies and procedures intended to reduce the risk of accidental destruction or loss, or the unauthorized disclosure or access to, such information, reasonably appropriate to the nature of the data concerned.

**Updates to Privacy Policy**

SW19, Inc.  may, in its sole discretion, update this Policy at any time and from time to time, by posting the amended Policy on this Site. The amended Policy shall be effective upon posting, and your access to or use of the Site following an update shall be deemed consent to the revised Policy.  If you have provided Personal Information to us, amendments to this Policy may (but are not required to) be sent to you via email or such other form of communication as you have requested.  We urge each visitor to refer back to this page regularly and especially prior to providing or updating any Personal Information.  This Policy may not be otherwise amended without the written consent of SW19, Inc..  This Policy was last updated on January 13, 2011.

**Contact, Questions, Comments, Complaints**

If you would like to communicate with SW19, Inc. regarding privacy issues or have questions, comments or complaints about this Policy or Site, please forward such communication to: [feedback@mariasharapova.com](mailto:feedback@mariasharapova.com)
